<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="UnstablePorto">
  <Package name="Missions">
    <Container name="Dialogues">
      <Key ID="STR_LL_Speaker_Informateur">
        <English>Informant</English>
        <French>Informateur</French>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="STR_LL_Task_02b_Narrative_Start">
        <English>HQ to patrol. Our informant has been taken by the militia. He's somewhere in the sector — locate him, eliminate his captors, and bring him out. He is critical to our intelligence network. Out.</English>
        <French>QG à patrouille. Notre informateur a été enlevé par la milice. Il se trouve quelque part dans le secteur — localisez-le, éliminez ses gardiens et exfiltrez-le. Il est crucial pour notre réseau de renseignement. Terminé.</French>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="STR_LL_Task_02b_Informateur_Freed">
        <English>They… they were going to execute me... Get me out of here.</English>
        <French>Ils… ils allaient m'exécuter... Sortez-moi d'ici.</French>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="STR_LL_Task_02b_Narrative_Success">
        <English>HQ to patrol. The informant is secure. Intel from him is being transmitted to command. Well done. Out.</English>
        <French>QG à patrouille. L'informateur est en sécurité. Les renseignements qu'il transmet sont acheminés vers le commandement. Bien joué. Terminé.</French>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="STR_LL_Task_02b_Narrative_Failed">
        <English>HQ to patrol. The informant has been killed. We have lost a critical intelligence source. The mission continues — our network is compromised. Out.</English>
        <French>QG à patrouille. L'informateur a été tué. Nous avons perdu une source de renseignement critique. La mission continue — notre réseau est compromis. Terminé.</French>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="STR_LL_Heli_Msg_Extract_Waiting_Hostage">
        <English>Waiting for informant to embark (%1m)...</English>
        <French>Attente embarquement de l'informateur (%1m)...</French>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="STR_LL_Heli_Msg_Extract_Players_Exit_Warning">
        <English>WARNING: Helicopter will not depart while players are on board! Get out!</English>
        <French>ATTENTION : L'hélicoptère ne partira pas tant qu'un joueur est à bord ! Sortez !</French>
      </Key>
    </Container>
  </Package>
</Project>
