<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Project name="UnstablePorto">
  <Package name="Missions">
    <Container name="Briefing">
      <Key ID="STR_LL_Diary">
        <English>Diary</English>
        <French>Journal</French>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="STR_LL_Briefing_Title">
        <English>Operations Order (OPORD)</English>
        <French>Ordre d'Opération (OPORD)</French>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="STR_LL_Briefing_Text">
        <English><![CDATA[<font size='16' color='#FFFF00'>OPERATION ROYAL ALLIANCE</font><br/><br/>
<font size='14' color='#00FF00'>1. SITUATION</font><br/>
The port island of Porto is facing severe ethnic, sectarian, and ideological tensions, fueled by poverty, local corruption, and clandestine migration routes. Armed insurgent groups, such as the ethnic nationalist Liberation Front (FL) and the jihadist Movement for Justice (MJ), are attempting to establish a rear logistics base and undermine the Sahrani Crown's authority. The RACS Multinational Expeditionary Corps is deployed to restore civil security and ensure the global pacification of the island.<br/><br/>
<font size='14' color='#00FF00'>2. MISSION</font><br/>
Conduct security operations, patrol urban areas, and neutralize insurgent threats through multiple successive tasks to ensure territorial control and civil safety in Porto. Meeting with a local militia leader is only one of the initial tasks intended to gather key intelligence on enemy networks.<br/><br/>
<font size='14' color='#00FF00'>3. SUPPORT</font><br/>
Initial transport is provided by the squad vehicle. During the operation, you will have access to on-demand air support, drone overwatch (MQ-9), and logistics supply drops for ammunition and replacement vehicles as needed. Good luck, Soldiers.]]></English>
        <French><![CDATA[<font size='16' color='#FFFF00'>OPÉRATION ROYAL ALLIANCE</font><br/><br/>
<font size='14' color='#00FF00'>1. SITUATION</font><br/>
L'île-port de Porto est en proie à de vives tensions ethniques, confessionnelles et idéologiques, catalysées par la pauvreté, la corruption locale et les flux migratoires clandestins. Des groupes armés insurgés, notamment le Front de Libération (FL) nationaliste ethnique et le Mouvement pour la Justice (MJ) djihadiste, tentent d'établir une base arrière et de saborder l'autorité de la Couronne de Sahrani. Le Corps Expéditionnaire Multinational du RACS est déployé pour restaurer la sécurité civile et assurer la pacification globale de l'île.<br/><br/>
<font size='14' color='#00FF00'>2. MISSION</font><br/>
Mener des opérations de sécurisation, patrouiller les zones urbaines et neutraliser les menaces insurgées à travers plusieurs tâches successives afin d'assurer le contrôle territorial et la sécurité civile de Porto. Le rendez-vous avec un chef de milice locale n'est qu'une des tâches initiales visant à obtenir des renseignements clés sur les réseaux ennemis.<br/><br/>
<font size='14' color='#00FF00'>3. SOUTIEN</font><br/>
Le transport initial est assuré par le véhicule d'escouade. Durant l'opération, vous disposez d'un soutien aérien à la demande, d'un survol permanent par drone (MQ-9), ainsi que de possibilités de livraisons logistiques de munitions et de véhicules de remplacement en cas de besoin. Bonne chance, soldats.]]></French>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="STR_LL_Diary_Context_Title">
        <English>Context and Situation</English>
        <French>Contexte et Situation</French>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="STR_LL_Diary_Context_Text">
        <English><![CDATA[<font size='16' color='#FFFF00'>GLOBAL CONTEXT</font><br/>
Following the difficult reunification of Sahrani, the Kingdom remains fragile. The radical ethnic nationalist North was defeated, but its clandestine networks and weapons survive.<br/>
The country has become a major Atlantic hub for illegal migration routes and arms/drug trafficking.<br/><br/>
The <font color='#00FF00'>RACS</font> has established a Multinational Expeditionary Corps integrating volunteers from allied nations (Turkey, Arab nations, Africa, Indonesia).<br/><br/>
<font size='16' color='#FFFF00'>TACTICAL SITUATION IN PORTO</font><br/>
Porto is a secondary port island suffering from deep ethnic, confessional, and ideological tensions, fueled by poverty, local corruption, and migration waves.]]></English>
        <French><![CDATA[<font size='16' color='#FFFF00'>CONTEXTE GLOBAL</font><br/>
Après la réunification difficile de Sahrani, le Royaume reste un État fragile. Le Nord nationaliste ethnique a été vaincu, mais ses réseaux clandestins et ses armes subsistent.<br/>
Le pays est devenu un hub en Atlantique pour les routes migratoires clandestines et les trafics d'armes et de drogue.<br/><br/>
Le <font color='#00FF00'>RACS</font> a instauré un Corps Expéditionnaire Multinational intégrant des volontaires de pays alliés (Turquie, pays arabes, Afrique, Indonésie).<br/><br/>
<font size='16' color='#FFFF00'>SITUATION TACTIQUE À PORTO</font><br/>
Porto est une île-port secondaire en proie à de vives tensions ethniques, confessionnelles et idéologiques, catalysées par la pauvreté, la corruption locale et les flux migratoires.]]></French>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="STR_LL_Diary_Factions_Title">
        <English>Factions</English>
        <French>Factions</French>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="STR_LL_Diary_Factions_Text">
        <English><![CDATA[<font size='16' color='#FF0000'>LIBERATION FRONT (FL)</font><br/>
Ethnic nationalist, anti-monarchist ideology. Recruits among those disappointed by the crown. Aims to expel the RACS from Porto.<br/><br/>
<font size='16' color='#FF0000'>MOVEMENT FOR JUSTICE (MJ)</font><br/>
Jihadist group linked to a transnational network. Aims to transform Porto into a logistics and smuggling sanctuary.<br/><br/>
<font size='16' color='#FF0000'>MILITIAS AND SMUGGLING CARTELS</font><br/>
Opportunistic criminals wanting to maintain local anarchy to protect their maritime trafficking.]]></English>
        <French><![CDATA[<font size='16' color='#FF0000'>FRONT DE LIBÉRATION (FL)</font><br/>
Idéologie nationaliste ethnique et anti-monarchiste. Recrute parmi les déçus de la couronne. Vise à chasser le RACS de Porto.<br/><br/>
<font size='16' color='#FF0000'>MOUVEMENT POUR LA JUSTICE (MJ)</font><br/>
Groupe djihadiste lié à un réseau transnational. Vise à faire de Porto un sanctuaire logistique et de contrebande.<br/><br/>
<font size='16' color='#FF0000'>MILICES ET CARTELS DE CONTREBANDE</font><br/>
Criminels opportunistes voulant maintenir l'anarchie locale pour pérenniser leurs trafics maritimes.]]></French>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="STR_LL_Diary_Lore_Title">
        <English>Narrative Background</English>
        <French>Historique Narratif</French>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="STR_LL_Diary_Lore_Text">
        <English><![CDATA[<font size='16' color='#FFFF00'>CAMPAIGN LORE (2025-2026)</font><br/>
Following deadly bombings on the mainland (Corazol market, Bagango outpost), Porto was identified as the main logistics hub for the MJ and FL.<br/><br/>
The King of Sahrani launched this autonomous pacification operation to prove that the multinational RACS is capable of stabilizing its territory without direct NATO or US intervention. <font color='#FFFF00'>This is a critical test for the Kingdom's credibility.</font>]]></English>
        <French><![CDATA[<font size='16' color='#FFFF00'>LORE DE CAMPAGNE (2025-2026)</font><br/>
Suite à des attentats sanglants sur le continent (marché de Corazol, poste de Bagango), Porto a été identifiée comme la plaque tournante logistique du MJ et du FL.<br/><br/>
Le Roi de Sahrani a lancé cette opération de pacification autonome pour prouver que le RACS multinational est capable de stabiliser son territory sans intervention directe de l'OTAN ou des États-Unis. <font color='#FFFF00'>C'est un test décisif pour la crédibilité du Royaume.</font>]]></French>
      </Key>
    </Container>
  </Package>
</Project>
